<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LoveNotties_v1</string>
    <string name="hlonipa">Hlonipa</string>
    <string name="dcIntro">At the heart of Nottingham Road, you\'ll find the Dream Centre, located within Midlands Community College. Here, we deliver training programs designed to eliminate the hurdles hindering individuals from entering the job market. Our mission centers around bridging the skills gap within our workforce.\n\nThrough engaging lectures, role-playing scenarios, assignments, and mentorships, our programs shape individuals into employable adults. We instill a resolute work ethic and a commitment to excellence, fostering a new generation of professionals poised for success.</string>
    <string name="dcCourseOne">This course strives to cultivate a resilient mindset in students. They are taught interview skills, how to effectively search for a job, managing time efficiently, financial and communication skills, developing strong employer - employee relations, and building values such as integrity and a strong work ethic for a professional setting.</string>
    <string name="dcCourseTwo">Designed for receptionists, personal assistants, and clerks, this course is tailored to enhance your administrative, communication, and technology proficiencies, preparing you to contribute in any office setting. The program covers a wide range of essential topics, including phone etiquette, customer relationship management, and general administrative skills, among others.</string>
    <string name="dcCourseThree">In today\'s working world, having a good understanding of computers is vital. Our program is here to ensure that students gain a strong foundation in fundamental computer skills. It\'s all about empowering you with the knowledge and confidence to navigate the digital landscape with ease, perfect for beginners or those looking to strengthen their computer capabilities.</string>
    <string name="dcContact">Contact:\ndreamcentrenotties@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="humanityFirstText">LoveNotties is dedicated to addressing the critical humanitarian needs within our community. Our primary focus revolves around ensuring food security and lending a helping hand within our community, particularly within local schools and at our Early Childhood Development Centres. \n\n We at LoveNotties aim to make a lasting and positive impact on the lives of those we serve.</string>
    <string name="HumanityER">We organize humanitarian aid for any Crisis Event that may arise</string>
    <string name="HumanityFD">We partner with local community members and organizations to supply basic food necessities</string>
    <string name="HumanityPHoles">We organize our community members to help fill and repair potholes in our community</string>
    <string name="HumanTokens">Together with our recycling program we offer a local token shop for those in need. People can exchange their recycing goods for tokens which can then be used to purchase items from our shop</string>
    <string name="HumanPartners">LoveNotties are partnered with many organizations to help improve our community. \n\nHopice\nSPCA\nGBV Champions\nJes Foord Foundation</string>
    <string name="LN_Motto">Respect for oneself, for others and for the environment.\nCaring for our Community</string>
    <string name="AboutUsInfo">LoveNotties is a Non Profit Company creating a catalyst for transformation. We aim to unite our community for positive change, as we believe we are better together.\n\nWe dream of a prosperous village where dreams are discovered and hope is renewed. A place of inspiration, joy and life. A community that know how to love and be loved.\n\nWe dream of a village where all races, genders, ages and classes live united, working together to benefit others and the environment.\n\nA place of opportunity, security and peace.\n\nA place of healing, belonging and trust.</string>
    <string name="InfoLocationText">Find Us at:\n 103 Old Main Road, Nottingham Road, 3280 (Midlands Animal Feeds)</string>
    <string name="ContactDetails">\nEmail: lovenotties@gmail.com\nCell: 065 – 738 5818\nShop hours: Fridays 09h00-16h00\nAddress: 103 Old Main Road, Nottingham Road, 3280</string>
    <string name="enviro_edu">Love Notties extends its reach through partnerships with schools and communities, promoting environmental education and awareness.\n\n These collaborations facilitate valuable programs that educate students and community members about the importance of environmental stewardship.\n\n By engaging with local schools and communities , Love Notties encourages people to make informed choices to protect the enviroment.</string>
    <string name="litter_clean_up">Love Notties is a dedicated champion for the environment, unwavering in its commitment to preserving the natural beauty of Nottingham.\n\n Through frequent litter clean-ups, the organization maintains clean streets, parks, and natural areas. Beyond clean-up efforts, they vigilantly monitor air, water, and soil quality, safeguarding both the ecosystem and residents.</string>
    <string name="recycling_center">Love Notties have established a recycling centre in Nottingham Road which operates every Friday from 9-12 am.\n\n The center caters for all types of materials to be recycled and reused in the Nottingham area.</string>
    <string name="parks_and_gardens">Love Notties works in close partnership with the Municipality and local environmental, parks, and gardens departments to enhance our region\'s aesthetics.\n\n They maintain road verges and gardens, ensuring an appealing environment that fosters community pride.\n\n Additionally, the organization actively combats invasive species, safeguarding the area\'s ecological balance.\n\n Love Notties\' multifaceted efforts contribute to a beautiful, thriving community</string>

</resources>